- 나야
- 그래
저런, 근사한데?
무슨 일이야?
Wow! You look nice.
What's the occasion?
모니카랑 10개월 되는 날이야
'장 조지'에 예약도 해뒀지
Monica and I are celebrating
our 10-month anniversary.
Got reservations at Jean-George.
How'd you get in?
- 거긴 힘들었을 텐데
- 전화 몇 통 하고 힘 좀 썼지
Made a few calls,
pulled some strings...
11시 반이야, 둘 다 치킨으로
통일하고 후식을 생략했거든
...and they'll seat us if we both
have chicken and don't get dessert.
-Hi, Chandler.
-Hey, Caitlin.
- 안녕, 챈들러
- 저런, 머리가 짧아졌네요?
Somebody got a haircut.
마음에 안 들어요
8살짜리 선머슴 같아요
I hate it. I look like
an 8-year-old boy.
그럼 체육시간이
엄청 신났을 텐데
If that was true, gym class
would've been more interesting.
-It's $27 even.
-Okay. Here you go.
- 27달러예요
- 네, 알았어요
Where's the chicken?
- 닭은 어디 갔죠?
- 뒤에요, 오리한테 삐쳤거든요
It's in the back.
The duck pissed him off.
달걀이 먼저라잖아요
He said that eggs came first.
- 고마워요, 또 봬요
- 네, 잘 가요
-Thanks. I'll see you later.
-Bye.
이게 뭐 하는 짓이야?
What the hell was that?
- 뭐가?
- 방금 새롱거렸잖아
-What?
-The flirting.
Aren't you supposed to be going out
with, let's see, my sister?
네 애인이 누구였더라?
내 동생 아냐?
- 새롱거린 적 없어
- 새롱거린 게 아니면!
I wasn't flirting.
It was totally flirting!
"Somebody got a haircut...."
'머리가 짧아졌네요
깨갱깽 깽깽... '
First of all, the impression?
Uncanny.
내 느낌부터 말하자면
참 괴기스럽다
Second, that wasn't flirting.
That was just casual conversation.
둘째, 새롱거린 게 아니라
지극히 일상적인 대화였어
- 대화 좋아하시네
- 새롱거림이란 이런 거야
Yeah, right.
You wanna see flirting?
I'll show you.
됐다, 됐어...
I'm good.
The One Where Ross Can't Flirt
조이 정말 대단하지?
'법과 질서'에 출연하다니
I am so proud of Joey.
-He's gonna be on Law and Order!
-I know.
누가 아니래
근데 '질서와 법'이 맞지 않니?
Don't you think it should
be called Order and Law?
No, because they arrest the guy
and then try him.
아니지, 체포한 다음
재판에 넘기잖아
Don't get me started on that.
누구 앞에서 아는 척일까
-I was not flirting.
-And on your anniversary. For shame!
새롱거린 거 아냐
그것도 기념일에
양심에 털 난 놈아!
What's going on?
왜 그래?
챈들러가 피자 배달
아가씨랑 노닥거렸대
He was hitting on
the hot delivery girl.
I was not. And oh, God!
얘가 진짜 일내겠네, 쉿!
You were. If anyone
should be hitting on her...
미안하지만 사실이야
여자랑 노닥거리는 건
짝 없는 사람이나 할 일이지
...it's the guy who's single...
...the guy who can do
something about it.
적어도 책임은 질 수 있잖아
Sounds like someone wants to be
Mr. Pizza Delivery Girl.
누군가 피자 배달
아가씨를 탐내는데?
그래서 이래?
케이틀린 맘에 들어?
Is that what this is about?
You like Caitlin?
Ross, we broke up two years ago.
You've been married since then.
우린 2년 전에 헤어졌어
넌 그 후로 결혼도 했고
I think it's okay
that we see other people.
다른 사람 만나도 되잖아?
I was watching her
at the pizza place.
전에 피자 가게에서
그 여자를 봤는데
And she was just so sexy and funny
and has the cutest little
너무 섹시하고 재미있고
그 조그맣고 귀여운...
그 여자 치수는 필요 없어
We don't need her measurements.
Pepperoni, pepperoni, pepperoni.
페퍼로니, 페퍼로니, 페퍼로니
로스, 네가 좋아하는
그 예쁜 여자 바보니?
She's pretty and you love her,
but is she stupid?
She forgot my vegetarian.
- 내 야채 피자가 없잖아
- 완벽한 기회다
This is perfect. She'll have
to come back here with your pizza.
네 피자를 갖고 다시 나타나면
이 로스가 마법을 걸어주겠어
And when she does,
I will turn on the charm "au" Ross.
I am so glad you don't eat meat.
너 고기 안 먹으니까 너무 좋다
See? Vegetarianism benefits everyone.
거봐, 채식주의는
모두한테 이로워
Hey, everybody, look who's here!
You remember my grandmother.
얘들아, 여기 좀 봐
우리 할머니 알지?
어서 오세요
-Big night!
-Yeah, it's so cool.
- 기대되시죠?
- 너무 잘됐어요
'법과 질서'에 나오는
손자가 자랑스러우시죠?
Joey on Law and Order.
You must be proud.
She doesn't understand
a word of English.
챈들러, 할머니는
영어 못 알아들으셔
I thought you were
Joey's other grandmother.
죄송해요, 조이의 다른
할머님이신 줄 알았어요
I've done it again.
이것도 영어네요
Nonnie's my biggest fan.
할머닌 내 열렬한 팬이셔
She's the only one in the family
who's always believed in me.
식구들 중에서 유일하게
날 믿어주는 분이지
Si. Big star.
그럼, 최고 스타지
My big fat Joey star.
우리 뚱땡이 조이 스타
Yeah, I weighed, like,
27 pounds when I was born.
난 태어나자마자
12킬로가 넘었거든
- 자기야, 우리 기념일이야
- 벌써 10개월이 됐군
-Happy anniversary!
-Happy anniversary, 10 months.
샤워하면서 런던에서의
첫날밤을 생각했거든
In the shower I was thinking
about our first night in London.
조이 할머님 오셨어
Joey's grandmother's right there.
-The one who speaks English?
-The one who doesn't.
영어 하시는 분?
못하시는 분?
못하시는 분
That was some hot love you gave me.
진짜 뜨거운 밤이었어
-I'll get ready.
-Wear those earrings I got you.
- 가서 준비할게
- 내가 준 귀걸이 해
That's a great idea. I was saving
them for something special.
그거 좋은 생각이다
특별한 날을 위해 아껴뒀지
-You've got to go home.
-But I like it here.
- 너 빨리 집에 가
- 난 이 집이 좋은데?
Get the earrings you borrowed.
He wants me to wear them.
전에 빌려준 귀걸이 가져와
챈들러가 오늘밤 그거 하래
I think they're in my purse.
Go get dressed and I'll look for them.
내 가방 속에 있을 거야
찾아볼 동안 가서 옷 입어
레이첼
I need those earrings you borrowed.
전에 빌려간 귀걸이 돌려줘
Yeah, I'll be right back.
알았어
금방 올게
Phoebe, you speak ltalian?
- 너 이태리어도 했어?
- 그런 것 같네
I guess so.
-Here you go.
-Thanks. Where's the other one?
- 잘 썼다, 고마워
- 잠깐, 나머지 한쪽은?
두 개 다 달라고?
Oh, what, you want both of them?
That's a little greedy, don't you think?
욕심이 좀 과하다
Rachel Karen Greene,
where's the other one?
레이첼 캐런 그린
나머지 한쪽 어쨌어?
알았어, 화내지 마
실은 잃어버렸어
Look, just don't freak out,
but I kind of lost it.
I know it's in the apartment,
but I definitely lost it.
분명 집안에 있는데
그게 어딘지 모르겠어
What'll I tell Monica?
She wants to wear them tonight.
모니카한테 뭐라고 해
오늘밤에 쓴다는데
- 자기 귀걸이 하면 되지
- 그게 모니카 귀걸이야
-Tell her to wear her own earrings.
-These are her earrings.
아니 되옵니다
You lent me her earrings?
I'm not allowed to borrow her stuff!
모니카 귀걸이였어?
난 걔 거 쓰면 안 돼
-Why not?
-Because I lose her stuff!
- 그건 왜?
- 맨날 잃어버리니깐!
You see that blind guy?
I'm gonna bash his head in later.
저 장님 있지?
이따 내가 머리를 후려치거든
My big scene's coming up.
The big scene coming up.
곧 저 나와요
곧 있으면 나온다구요
'고동 이 쑤시면 나온다' 해도
별 차이 없을 것 같다
If you said, "Big lima bean bubbling up,"
would she know the difference?
What are you doing?
레이첼, 뭐하니?
Oh, I just can't watch.
It's too scary.
너무 무서워서 못 보겠어
It's a diaper commercial.
기저귀 광고야
Yeah, well, you know me.
Babies, responsibilities....
내가 그렇잖아
애들 키울 거 생각하면...
꺄악!
- 피자 왔습니다
- 저요! 제가 나갈게요!
-Pizza delivery.
-I'll get it! I will get that!
How does my hair look?
내 머리 어때?
Ross, it hasn't moved since 1996.
그 머리는 1996년
이후로 고정불변이야
- 안녕하세요
- 어서 와요
One vegetarian pizza.
It's 12.50.
야채 피자 하나
12달러 50센트예요
저기, 위로가 될지 모르지만
난 8살짜리 선머슴 좋아해요
By the way, if it makes
you feel any better...
...I happen to like
8-year-old boys.
What?
- 네?
- 제 말은 그게 아니라...
Your hair.
Before. Your hair.
아까 그 머리가 8살짜리
선머슴 같다고 했잖아요
You said you thought your hair
looked like an 8-year-old boy's...
그게 좋다는 거예요
...and I'm just saying I like it.
그 머리요
The hair.
Thanks.
감사합니다
You understand, I don't actually
like 8-year-old boys.
진짜로 8살짜리 선머슴을
좋아하는 건 아니에요
빨리 돈이나 주세요
All I'm looking for is the money.
Here you go.
Stop bringing us pizzas, you.
여기, 이제 우리 집에
배달 오지 말아요
애써보죠
I'm gonna try.
You're welcome.
- 고마워할 거 없어
- 잘되는 거 도저히 못 보겠냐?
You couldn't let me have her,
could you?
- 뭐?
- 내가 좋아하는 거 알면서도
This is a girl I really like,
and you had to swoop in there!
야비하게 쏙 끼어드는구만
What?
왜들 그래?
얘가 피자 배달 아가씨랑
까놓고 새롱거린단다
Chandler was flirting
with the hot delivery girl.
지적 감사합니다
Thank you for that.
I was not flirting.
- 새롱거린 적 없어
- 난 상관없어, 괜찮아
It's okay. I don't care.
That's fine.
Really?
- 정말로?
- 진짜로?
별일도 아니잖아
난 늘 그러는데
It's no big deal.
I do it all the time.
그러니까 넌 늘 남자들이랑
새롱거린다고?
You flirt with guys all the time?
It doesn't mean anything. Just like
it doesn't mean anything with you.
그럼, 아무 뜻도 없잖아
자기한텐 무슨 의미가 있나?
그건 경우가 달라
넌 나보다 잘 나가니까
There's a difference.
You're a lot hotter.
지당한 말씀
True story.
그게 그렇게 신경 쓰여?
This actually bothers you?
그래, 신경 쓰여
남들은 안 그러나?
Yes, and I think
it'd bother a lot of people.
When you and Ross dated...
레이첼, 전에 로스가 다른
여자랑 새롱거리면 화났지?
...did it bother you
when he flirted with other women?
아니, 다른 여자랑
붙어먹으면 화나더라
No, it bothered me when
he slept with other women.
And thank you for that.
지적 고맙다
I never had to worry.
실은 걱정할 필요가 없었어
로스는 그 방면엔 소질 없거든
He was never good
at the flirting thing.
뭐? 그게....
무슨 소리야?
너한텐 통했는데
What are you talking about?
It worked with you.
No, you're right.
맞아, 그렇지
만나서 새롱거리고...
We met, you flirted and then bam!
Nine years later, you had me.
빵! 9년 만에 날 손에 넣었지
All right.
그래, 좋아
나 지금 피자 한 판
더 시킬 거야
You know what I'll do?
I'll order another pizza.
And when Caitlin gets here...
케이틀린이 오면
내 실력을 보여주겠어
...I will show you how well I flirt.
그 여자 전화번호도 알아내지
가게 전화번호 말고
I will get her phone number.
And not the one on the menu.
-I found it.
-Thank God! Where was it?
찾았어
- 살았다! 어디서?
- 네 방 서랍
On your dresser.
이건 원래 있던 한쪽이야
Okay, that is the one we already have.
Here's my big scene.
My big scene's here.
얘들아, 이제 나온다
-Wanna bet nobody heard anything?
-No bet.
- 목격자가 있을까?
- 포기하세요
Anybody home?
계십니까?
- 돌겠네...
- 왜?
-Oh, my God.
-What?
아뇨... 계속 웃어라
할머니 눈치 채면 돌아가신다
Everybody keep smiling. It'll kill
my grandmother if she finds out.
What is it?
- 뭔데 그래?
- 나 잘렸다
They cut me out of the show.
What?
뭐?
- 확실해?
- 아직 안 나왔겠지
-Are you sure?
-Maybe your scene's coming up.
그건 아냐
저 시체 주머니 보여?
Not likely. Because you see
that body bag right there?
- 그래
- 나 그 안에 있어
I'm in it.
큰일 났네
어떡할 거야?
This is terrible.
What'll you do?
모르겠어
나만 보고 사신 분인데
I don't know. This little
old lady lives for my career.
'생의 나날들'에서 잘렸을 때
사경을 헤매셨다니까
When they dumped me off
Days of Our Lives, she almost died.
That's not good.
그럼 심각한데
- 간병인까지 구했지 뭐야
- 세상에!
-Yeah, we had to get her a home nurse.
-Oh, my God.
돈이 무진장 들어갔어
Yeah, she almost died
and got really expensive.
넌 왜 안 웃어?
안 돼, 모두 웃어
You're not smiling. Not that face!
Everybody smile!
Just tell her what happened.
It's not your fault.
그냥 사실대로 말씀드려
네 잘못도 아니잖아
우리 계속 이러면
겁에 질려 돌아가시겠다
If we keep talking this way,
won't we freak her out soon?
금방 나와요
곧 나올 거예요
Soon. I'm gonna be on soon.
There I am!
여기다!
아냐, 샘 워터스턴
Sam Waterston!
No, no. That's me.
That's me!
아뇨, 저라니까요
No. Sam Waterston.
아니다, 샘 워터스턴
Crime Misdemeanor, Capricorn One.
'사소한 범죄'
'카프리콘 원'
'헬로'는 모르는 분이
'카프리콘 원'은 아시네
She doesn't know "hello,"
but she knows Capricorn One.
I need those earrings.
We're leaving when the show's over.
피비, 빨리 귀걸이 줘
저거 끝나는 대로 갈 거야
But I already gave them back to you.
벌써 돌려줬잖아
No, you didn't.
안 줬어
맞아, 벌써 안 돌려줬어
그렇게 말했잖아
I already didn't gave them back to you.
That's what I said.
Where's that other earring?
- 나머지 한쪽은 어떻게 됐어?
- 여기 없나 봐, 어떡하니?
It's not here, Phoebe.
It's not here.
참! 간밤에 나
챈들러 집에 갔다
I went to Chandler's last night.
챈들러 보석함도 꼭 확인해
Make sure you check
Chandler's jewelry box.
Chandler has a jewelry box?
챈들러한테 보석함이 있어?
We have 10 minutes. Do you
want me to get into that now?
10분밖에 안 남은 상황에서
그 사연을 꼭 풀어야겠니?
Hey, Phoebe.
- 안녕, 피비
- 그래
How's that...
아까 그 야채 피자가
입에는 좀 맞았니?
...vegetarian pizza
working out for you?
You and those vegetables
have a real...
너랑 야채는 상당히
잘 어울린다, 그치?
...thing going on, huh?
Why are you being weird?
너 좀 이상하다
Do you like it?
마음에 들어?
No. That'd be,
"Why are you being cute?"
마음에 들면
이상하다고 했겠니?
Okay. I'm working on my flirting.
- 새롱거리기 훈련이야
- 오, 그걸 몰랐네
I did not get that.
So, Monica, do you like
Law and Order?
- 모니카, '법과 질서' 좋아해?
- 그래, 괜찮아
Yeah, it's good.
오늘 새로운 걸 많이 배운다
네가 '법과 질서'를 좋아하고
I found out all this stuff about you.
You like Law and Order...
...and you've flirted with every guy
in the tri-state area.
걸리는 남자마다
새롱거린다는 거
Okay, let me get this straight.
그럼 정리를 해보자
It's okay for you to flirt,
but not for me?
넌 새롱거려도 괜찮고
난 안 된다?
I'm glad we cleared that up.
확실하게 정리됐네
I'm sorry, but some things are
different for men and women.
미안하지만 남자랑 여자는 달라
- 계속해 봐, 뭐가 다른데?
- 입이 닳도록 얘기했지만 좋아
Teach me about men and women.
I've already taught you
so much already, but whatever.
When you flirt with a guy,
you think, "No big deal."
넌 별 뜻 없이 남자랑
새롱거린다고 하지만
But he thinks, "Finally!
Somebody who wants to sleep with me."
남자는 그런 여자를
잠자리 상대로 생각해
-No way!
-It's true.
- 말도 안 돼
- 사실이야
-Well, that's pathetic.
-Again, true.
- 너무 치사하다
- 역시 사실이야
-This goes for all guys?
-All guys that are awake.
- 남자들은 다 그래?
- 깨어있는 남자라면
We go to sleep.
우리가 잠들면 지구 반대편
남자들이 일어나서 똑같은 짓을 해
All guys from the other end of the
world wake up and act the same way.
It's another commercial
and I still haven't told her.
어쩌냐, 또 광고하는데
아직도 말씀 못 드렸어
저게 마지막 광고야
Joey, this is the last commercial.
-You got 10 minutes left.
-I know!
- 10분밖에 안 남았어
- 나도 알아, 어떡하지?
What am I gonna do?
You will not run out
and leave her here.
할머니 남겨두고
달아나기만 해봐?
Yeah, all right.
알았어
조이?
Joey's gonna be right back.
Right back?
곧 돌아올 거예요
곧 온다구요
Meanwhile, let's talk about you.
막간을 이용해 할머님 얘기나 하죠
참 작고 연로하시네요
So you're old and small.
-Did you find it?
-The earring, no.
찾았어?
귀걸이는 없고 소파 밑에
내 선글라스가 있더라
But I found my sunglasses.
I've been looking for these
since last summer.
지난여름부터 찾았는데
Those are mine.
You borrowed them from me.
내 선글라스야
네가 빌려갔잖아
Okay. Calm down.
Here they are.
진정해라, 주면 되잖아
피비?
-What do we do?
-I don't know. I don't know!
- 어떡해...
- 나도 모르겠어
We'll just have
to tell Monica, that's all.
할 수 없지 뭐
그냥 사실대로 털어놓자
Oh, God! She's gonna kill me.
날 죽이려 들 텐데
- 내 잘못이라고 말할게
- 그럼 너무 좋지
I could tell her it was all my fault.
Oh, that'd be great.
Mon, could I talk to you?
- 모니카, 나 좀 볼래?
- 그래, 뭔데?
Yeah. What is it?
I lost one of your earrings.
네 귀걸이 한쪽 잃어버렸어
미안해, 정말 미안하다
I'm sorry. I am so, so sorry.
All right, what can you do?
If you lost it, you lost it.
괜찮아, 어쩌겠니...
이미 잃어버린 건데
내가 다른 걸로 꼭 사줄게
미안해서 어떡하니
I'll replace it. I promise.
I feel so terrible.
- 일부러 그런 것도 아닌데 뭐
- 그야 그렇지
That's fine.
You didn't do it on purpose.
Look at you. Come here.
그러다 울겠다
-You feel better?
-Yeah. You're the best.
- 좀 나아?
- 그래, 너밖에 없다
Okay, wait a minute.
잠시 대기
I can't do this.
아무래도 안 되겠다
사실은 피비 잘못이 아냐
Listen, honey,
it's not Phoebe's fault.
She lent me the earrings.
얘가 나한테 빌려줬는데
내가 잃어버렸어, 미안해
I lost it. I'm so sorry, honey.
I feel terrible too.
이 일을 어떡하니
이래서 너한테는
안 빌려주는 거야
That is exactly why
I do not lend you stuff!
First, my jewelry.
If it's not that, it's my sweater.
내 보석에다 파란색 스웨터
그것도 모자라 선글라스까지
And if it's not that,
it's my sunglasses.
Your sunglasses?
- 네 선글라스?
- 그래
주면 되잖아
Oh, right.
-Pizza.
-Mine, mine, mine!
- 피자예요
- 저요! 접니다!
Okay, here goes.
자, 기대하시라
Prepare yourselves
for some class-A flirting.
특급 여자 후리기
관람 준비하세요
Okay, hold on.
그래, 잠깐만
됐다
하지 마, 정말 그 여자가
좋다면 이러는 거 아냐...
If you really like this girl, I don't
think flirting is the right way
You'll see.
두고 봐, 좋았어
What's her name?
이름이 뭐였더라?
Caitlin!
- 케이틀린
- 케이틀린!
왔군요
이렇게 먹어대면 곤란한데
We can't keep eating like this.
It's $12.50.
- 12달러 50센트예요
- 알았어요
헌데...
Do you make the pizzas in one
of those wood-burning ovens?
피자는 장작 때는
오븐에서 굽나요?
No, actually, I think they're gas.
아뇨, 아마 가스일 거예요
가스? 와우!
Gas?
Intense.
강렬하네요
If this is how all the Gellers flirt,
we don't have a problem.
겔러 집안 새롱거림이
저거라면 우린 괜찮아
저기...
가스 냄새 있죠?
You know that smell gas has?
- 네
- 첨가한 거래요
They put that in.
-What?
-The gas is odorless.
- 네?
- 가스는 냄새가 없는데
But they add the smell
so you know when there's a leak.
새면 알 수 있도록
일부러 첨가한 거죠
Well, okay.
알았어요
A lot of other gas smells.
냄새나는 가스도 많아요
Oh, the humanity!
인간 냄새 물씬 풍긴다
Methane smells....
메탄도 냄새나고...
You know what?
Actually, I really should go.
전 이만 가봐야겠어요
- 아직 계산을 안 했는데
- 아뇨, 괜찮아요
-But I haven't paid you yet.
-That's okay.
무더기로 주문하셨으니
이번엔 제가 사죠 뭐
You guys have ordered so many
that this one's on me.
Was I talking to her about gas?
나 방금 가스 얘기했니?
More so than anything else.
다른 주제는 없었다고 봐야지
난 꽤 재미있더라
I found it interesting.
I'm sorry.
- 기운 내
- 아니, 걱정할 거 없어
Don't worry about it.
In nine years, she and l
will be right there!
9년 후면 저 여자는
내 손안에 있소이다
그래, 난 이 상자나
버리고 와야겠다
I'm gonna clear out
some of these boxes.
- 로스?
- 왜?
What else do they add smell to?
냄새 첨가하는 거 또 없니?
Caitlin! Caitlin!
저기, 잠깐만
Hi, I'm Rachel.
난 레이첼이에요
- 저 위층에 피자 시킨 집
- 뭐가 잘못됐나요?
The people with all the pizza.
Was there a problem?
아뇨, 괜찮아요
피자도 좋고
No, they're fine. Great pizza.
But, actually, my friend Ross...
내 친구 로스 말인데요
...he gets nervous when he's flirting.
여자랑 새롱거릴 땐
늘 저렇게 긴장해요
Oh, my God!
맙소사!
그게 새롱거린 거예요?
That was flirting?
나도 잘 알아요, 하지만
일단 그 시기를 넘기면...
I know, I know.
I'm telling you,
once you get past that part...
물론 당시엔 죽고 싶지만
정말 좋은 사람이에요
...where it feels
like you wanna die...
...he's a really good person.
The guy with the gas?
가스 얘기하는 남자가?
네, 얼마나 착하고
재미있는지 몰라요
I'm telling you, he's really
sweet and really funny...
...and he's just got a good heart.
마음도 정말 따뜻하고
You know, actually, I did think that
he was cute and then he started talking.
사실 나도 괜찮은
남자라고 생각했어요
입 열기 전에는요
See, there you go.
제대로 봤네요
그쪽을 진심으로
좋아하는 것 같아요
-Besides, I think he really likes you.
-Really?
정말이에요?
사람은 일곱인데 피자를
왜 열 판이나 시켰겠어요
Well, we have seven people
and 10 pizzas. What do you think?
I thought Joey was there.
조이가 있어서
그런 거 아닌가요?
Yeah, no, but just I'm telling you
he's worth a shot.
만나봐도 후회는
절대 안 할 거예요
Well, if he's so great
why don't you go out with him?
그렇게 좋은 사람이면
그쪽이 사귀지 그래요
Well, you know, at some point...
그러고 보니 나중에 시간 내서
좀 더 긴 대화를 나눠야겠네요
...you and I may need
to have a longer conversation.
Hey, Ross?
로스?
I just ran into Caitlin
in the hallway.
복도에서 케이틀린을 봤는데
You must be getting better at
this flirting stuff than I thought.
네 실력도 그런대로
괜찮은 모양이더라
-What?
-I don't get it, but she wanted me...
무슨 뜻이야?
아무튼 이 전화번호
너한테 전해달래
...to give you her number.
- 그냥 이걸 줬어?
- 그래
And she just gave you this?
Rach, thanks. But I don't need
you doing me any favors.
레이첼, 고맙지만
일부러 이럴 거 없어
난 아무 것도 안 했어
네가 마음에 든대
I didn't.
She thought you were cute.
Well, that I can believe.
- 그건 말이 되네
- 그럼
Hey, is the show still on?
- 아직 안 끝났어?
- 다 돼간다
Almost over, man.
Hey, Nonnie.
할머니
- 저기 교황님 아냐?
- 어디?
Is that the pope?
Why am I looking?
내가 뭐하는 거지?
Oh, here I am!
This is my big scene.
할머니, 보세요
제가 나왔어요
All right, back off!
좋아, 물러서
I got a gun!
여기 총도 있어
못 쏠 줄 알아?
I'm not afraid to use it.
- 오, 조이
- 네, 저예요
That's right, Nonnie.
셔츠나 갈아입지 그랬냐
You couldn't have at least
changed your shirt?
10만 달러가 든 가방을 준비...
저리 가, 훠이
Now, I want a suitcase
filled with $ 100,000
Filled with $ 100,000
in small bills.
빳빳한 소액권으로 10만 달러다
내 요구를... 훠이!
And if I don't get
Shoo!
And if I don't get it...
내 요구를 묵살하면...
...I'll shoot this duck!
이 오리를 쏘겠다
안 돼
Oh, no!
I'm coming out!
지금 나간다
저걸 믿으실까?
And she's supposed to buy this?
조이, 브라보!
벨리시모!
Ground control to Major Tom
여기는 관제탑
톰 소령 들어라
Commencing countdown
카운트다운 개시
엔진...
Engines
On
점화
That's scenes from next week's show.
Next week.
저건 다음주 예고편이에요
I am definitely gonna watch that.
놓치지 말고 봐야지
Do these look the same?
- 어때? 똑같아 보여?
- 빼다 박았네
-Definitely.
-Not as each other.
- 이 두 개를 비교하지 말고
- 그럼 아니지
Then, no.
- 이제 갈까?
- 그래
-Hey, you ready?
-Yeah.
You look amazing.
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
정말 예뻐, 난 세상에서
제일 운 좋은 남자야
이따가 운 더 좋아질 거야
You're about to get
a little luckier.
-Let me see the earrings.
-Right, the earrings.
- 귀걸이 좀 봐
- 그래, 여기...
They look great.
너무 근사해
그 애인 안목 한번 높다
Does your boyfriend have
the best taste or what?
My boyfriend really does
have great taste.
맞아, 보는 눈 진짜 높지
Thanks for picking out the earrings.
귀걸이 골라줘서 고맙다